Dorothy Feola collection on lesbian and feminist publications, circa 1970-1986.
Dorothy Feola collection on lesbian and feminist publications, circa 1970-1986
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dorothy Feola Collection of lesbian and feminist publications, circa 1970-1986.
7303
Dorothy Feola
1 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Book catalogs, publicity materials on lesbian, gay, and feminist issues, newsletters and other materials from chapters of the National Organization for Women, items relating to publishing, and newsletters of interest to Feola such as The Animals' Agenda and Family Planning Perspectives
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dorothy Feola served as the editor of the WOMEN'S NETWORK.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Book catalogs, publicity materials on lesbian, gay, and feminist issues, newsletters and other materials from chapters of the National Organization for Women, items relating to publishing, and newsletters of interest to Feola such as The Animals' Agenda and Family Planning Perspectives. As editor of the Women's Network, she collected books and journals of feminist and lesbian poetry and local lesbian and feminist newsletters from all regions of the United States and several titles from Canada. Her collected feminist and lesbian periodicals (over 50 titles filling 9 cubic feet) and books were cataloged as individual titles.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Feola, Dorothy.; National Organization for Women.
Titles:
Women's Network.
Subjects:
Feminists--Periodicals.; Lesbians--Periodicals.; Lesbianism.; Lesbians' writings, American.; Feminism.; Feminist literature.; Feminist poetry.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- About Laddie Hoster, editor, "Wishing Well", 1979 (Box 1)
- Alternatives (Box 1)
- Animals' Agenda, The, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
- Archives, 1980s (Box 1)
- Black Women's Relationships Project, National Coalition of Black Gays (Box 1)
- Book Catalogs, 1974-1980 (Box 1)
- Book Catalogs and Eve's Garden, 1981-1989 (Box 1)
- Bronx NOW, 1970s (Box 1)
- Brooklyn NOW, 1970s (Box 1)
- Directory of Women's Media, 1985 (Box 1)
- Dorthy Feola biographical material, Women's Network files (Box 1)
- Health, 1980s (Box 1)
- Issues in Brief, 1980s (Box 1)
- News--Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1982-1985 (Box 1)
- Miscellany (Box 1)
- New York State NOW (Box 1)
- Poetry--Miscellany (Box 1)
- Political, 1982-1986 (Box 1)
- Political, New York, 1980-1986 (Box 1)
- Publicity and Broadsides, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Publicity, 1977-1986 (Box 1)
- Publicity: Desert Heart Productions, 1980 (Box 1)
- Publicity: "Nine to Five", 1980 (Box 1)
- Publicity: Cris Williamson, 1981 (Box 1)
- Publicity: "The G Spot" by Alice Kahn Ladas et al., 1982 (Box 1)
- Publishing (Box 1)
- Writer's Digest, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
- Writer's Digest, 1975 (Box 1)
- Womyn's Peace Caravan, 1984 (Box 1)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Periodicals - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
Atlanta, v.8 no.12; v.9 no. 6, no.8
ACLU Women's Rights Report, v.1 no.4; v.2 no. 1-2; v.3 no.1
Against the Wall, v.8 no.3, no.7
Albatross, 1975-03, 1985-04
All She Wrote, 1983-01; 1983-02; Spring 1984
Alternatives Corner Newsletter, 1985-03 to 1987-01 (Date range not complete)
Amazon Quarterly, v.2 no.3, no.4; v.3 no.1, no.2
Among Friends, v.2 no.4, no.6
Astraea Foundation Bulletin, Fall 1982 to Spring 1986Fall and Spring issues only; date range not complete
Austindyke, v.2 no.1, no.4-9
Bear & Company, v.1 no.8
Le Berdache, no. 20-31 (Date range not complete)
Best Friends, no.4, no.5
Big Apple Dyke News, v.1 no.1, no.3-5
Big Mama Rag, v.4 no.9
Brooklyn College Women's Center, v.1 no.1; Spring 1986
Broomstick, 1978-12 to 1979-02; v.1 no.5-6; v.4 no.3-5; v.5 no.1
Bulletin, 1978-12 to 1981-03 (Date range not complete)
Ca s'attrape!!, v.1 no.1-4; v.2 no.9; v.3 no.1
Chrysalis, no.1
Circle, v.3 no.4
City Women, 1977-04 to 1977-05
Common Ground, n.d.; 1979-03 to 1979-05; 1981-02
Common Lives/Lesbian Lives, no.2, no.12, no.14-16
Communiqu'elles, v.7 no.3-4; v.8 no.8; v.9 no.1; v.10 no.3-5
Conditions, v.1 no.1-3; v.3 no.2-3
Connexions, no.10
COSMEP Newsletter, v.11 no.8; v.12 no.2, no.6-9
Craftswimmin's Mutual Aid Society, 1985-06; 1985-09; 1986-05
Crosswinds, no.38-53; no.77-78 (Date range not complete)
Dialog, 1978-07; Fall 1978
Dinah, 1978-08 to 1981-10 (Date range not complete)
Dyke: A Quarterly, v.1 no.1-4, no.8
Eidos, v.1 no.4; v.3 no.1
Electric Circle, v.1 no.1
Feminist Art Journal, v.5 no.4, v.6 no.1
Feminist Bulletin, v.10 no.2-7; v.11 no.1, v.12 no.4, no.10, no.12
Feminist Studies, v.4 no.1-3; v.5 no.3
Feminist Writers' Guild, 1978-01 to 1985-03 (Date range not complete)
Fighting Woman News, no.10; v.3 no.1; v.6 no.2; v.8 no.4
Focus, 1975-01 to 1975-12; 1981-02 (Date range not complete)
The Freewoman, v.3 no.1, no.3-6
Gaia's Guide, 1976; 1977; 1979
A Gay Person's Guide to New England, 1975
Gay Teachers Association Newsletter, v.1 no.2; v.1 no.7/8
Gayellow Pages for New York/New Jersey, no.15, no.18, no.19
Grapevine, Summer 1979 to Fall 1983 (Date range not complete)
Gravida, no. 5-7, no. 9, no. 11-12, special issue
Harpies, v.1 no. 1, 5
Heracane, v.1 no.1
In The Life, no.1-2
International Journal of Women's Studies, v.1 no.3-5
Jane Doe, 1984-11, 1985-05
Landward Ho!, v.7 no.4, 6
Lavender Morning, v.2 no.1, 3, 6
Lavender Woman, v.2 no.2-3
Leaping Lesbian, v.1 no.6, 9; v.2 no.2, 3, 5, 6
Le'sbeinformed, 1977-02 to 1980-04 (Date range not complete)
Lesbian Center Newsletter, no.9, 11
Lesbian Community News, 1981-01-19 and n.d.
Lesbian Connection, v.1 no.2-8; v.2 no.1-8; v.3 no.1, 3; v.4 no.3-5; v.5 no.1, 5-6; v.6 no.1-4; v.7 no.4; v.8 no.3, 5; v.9 no.3, 4 (Also includes some unnumbered winter supplement/catalog issues)
Lesbian Feminist, 1976-04 to 1978-10 (Date range not complete)
Lesbian Insider Insighter Inciter, no. 2-5, 9
Lesbian News, no.37-48; v.5 no.10-12; v.6 no.4, 6, 7, 9; v.7 no.12; v.8 no.1, 5-8; v.9 no.1, 4, 7
Lesbians Rising, 1977-06 to winter 1981 (Date range not complete)
Lesbian Tide, 1975-01 to 1980-04 (Date range not complete)
Lesbian Voices, v.1 no.2 and n.d.
Liberated Women's Appointment Calendar, 1975 to 1976
Lifeline, no.41, 44, 45, 48
Light: A Poetry Review, v.1 no.2; no.4, 5
Mad Moose Gazette, v.10 no.2, 4
Majority Report, v.6 no.14; v.7 no.5, 12, 17; v.8 no.14
Makara, v.1 no.5
Margins, no.23
Matriarchist, v.1 no.4; v.2 no.1
Matrices, v.1 no.1-3; v.3 no.1-2; v.4 no.1, 3; v.5 no.1-2 and n.d.
Media Report to Women, v.8 no.4; v.10 no.4, 7, 8
Mid-Hudson Valley AIDS Task Force, 1985-09
Modus Operandi, 1977-06, 1979-08
Mom's Apple Pie, 1974-11 to Fall 1985 (Date range not complete)
Moonstorm, v.3 no.1; no.9-18 (Date range not complete)
Motheroot Journal, v.4 no.3-4; v.5 no.1
My Secret Life in the Mail, no.5, 6, 8
National Women's Political Caucus Newsletter, v.4 no.1-6
Neighborhood Women, v.1 no.4; v.3 no.1
New Women's Times, v.6 no.13, 19, 20; v.7 no.2
New Women's Times Feminist Review, no.1, 12-15
North Shore Women, 1978-11 to 1982-02 (Date range not complete)
off our backs, v.8 no.6-8
The Other Paper, v.1 no.6, 7; v.3 no.3
Our Own, v.2 no.2-4; v.3 no.1, 3; v.4 no.3
Pearl Diver, 1977-05
Pedestal, v.7 no.1, 3
Plexus, v.4 no.9; v.5 no.4-8; v.7 no.6, 8, 11
Primavera, 1975, 1976
Pointblank Times, v.3 no.5; v.4 no.1, 2
POW (Poetry Organization for Women), 1978-11 to 1980-03 and n.d. (Date range not complete)
Quest, v.3 no.3
Reflections, v.1 no.2, 8, 9
Reproductive Rights Newsletter, no.5, 6
San Francisco Women's Switchboard & Women's Centers, 1978-10 to 1979-08 (Date range not complete)
Second Wave, Summer 1971 to 1980 (Date range not complete)
She, v.2 no.4; v.3 no.2-6
Signs, v.5 no.1
Sinister Wisdom, v.1 no.2; no.3-7, 11-15
Sisters United, 1979-09 to Winter 1982 (Date range not complete)
So's Your Old Lady, v.2 no.1; no.8, 10, 14, 18
Southern California Women for Understanding, v.4 no.6; v.6 no.4, 5; v.7 no.1, 3
Speak Out!, v.4 no.3, v.5 no.2
Spokeswoman, v.10 no.11-12; v.11 no.2
S Lambda Quarterly, v.1 no.1-3; v.2 no.1-3
Sunbury, no.1-9
Syzygy, 1976 and n.d.
Telewoman, 1980-01 to 1985-10 (Date range not complete)
Thesmophoria, v.4 no.5, 7; v.6 no.6-8; v.7 no.1-3, 8; v.8 no.1-2
Thirteenth Moon, v.1 no.2; v.2 no.1-2; v.3 no.1-2; v.4 no.1-2
Thursday's Child, 1978-11 to 1982-11 (Date range not complete)
Treize, v.1 no.3-6; v.2 no.1, 2-5; v.3 no.1-3
Unicorn, 1981 quarters 1-3
Voices, no.1, 2, 8
Washout, v.1 no.1-4
What She Wants, v.8 no.7; v.9 no.2
West Sider, 1978-02 to 1980-05 (Date range not complete)
Wishing Well, Fall 1979 to 1984-03 (Date range not complete)
Witch and the Chameleon, no.4-6
W74, v.3 no.5, 6, 8
Woman to Woman, v.1 no.6, 7
Womankind, v.2 no.7, 14-16
Womanews, v.1 no.7, 11; v.2 no.1, 2, 4, 7